gainesvillesbest.com 2018-06-13

# Kaspersky Coupon 2013 2014 Get 50 OFF Antivirus Internet Security - Privacy Policy

Kaspersky Coupon Usage Instructions:

1) _**Click**_ on the Kaspersky coupons above to _CLAIM THE OFFER_ \- The Kaspersky promotional offer will _OPEN IN A NEW TAB_.

2) Paste _**kaspersky2011**_ as your Kaspersky COUPON CODE in order to enjoy an additional 10% discount ON TOP OF THE OFFER. (Clicking on the coupons above will automatically copy the coupon on your clipboard.)  

Save more money on Kaspersky - use our Kaspersky coupon today! 

|  Privacy Policy  |  [ ](http://gainesvillesbest.com/blog/index2.php?option=com_content&do_pdf=1&id=1 "PDF") |  [ ](http://gainesvillesbest.com/blog/index2.php?option=com_content&task=view&id=1&pop=1&page=0&Itemid=3 "Print") |  [ ](http://gainesvillesbest.com/blog/index2.php?option=com_content&task=emailform&id=1&itemid=3 "E-mail")  
---|---|---|---  
  
gainesvillesbest.com takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. See this privacy policy primer to learn more about privacy policies in general.

Routine Information Collection

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

Cookies and Web Beacons

Where necessary, gainesvillesbest.com uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

Controlling Your Privacy

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. This list of web browser privacy management links may also be useful.

Contact Information

Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to [info@planetfreeiq.com](mailto:info@planetfreeiq.com) for further clarification.

This privacy policy was generated by the Privacy Policy for WordPress plugin.

---  
  
[ Back ] 

|  Main Menu   
---  
---  
Syndicate   
---
